EXEC [dbo].[_CodeGenerator]
	@TableName = 'Script', --Actual database table name
	@TableShortName = 'S', --Table short name, if table name is UserRole then short name is UR
	@PKFieldName = 'Id', --Table primary key field name
	@AlreadyExistFields = 'Name BseCode NseCode ISINCode', --Already exists check field list by space seperated while insert or update
	@IsTransactionApply = 0,
	@ClsTableName = 'Script', --Class name except word cls and Business, Entity, Controller means if you enter User then Business > clsUserBusiness, Entity > clsUserEntity, model > UserModel etc...
	@AddLOVs = '', --Singular table name list by space sperated for page add/edit mode
	@ListLOVs = '', --Singular table name list by space sperated for page list mode
	@MainColumns = 'Id Name', --Main fields list by space seperated for LOV
	@ParameterColumns = 'Id Name BseCode NseCode', --Field list by space seperated for create where part and parameter class
	@Namespace = 'Master.Script', --Class namespace for generete namespace and routes
	@DevelopmentBy	= 'Rekansh Patel' --Developer name